ICC Lombard please give your opinion on this chart
sir, it was a little weaker than expected, the
result is not very special, net
premium income went up by 12%, profit is also
up by 12%, claim ratio has increased a little,
however there is a decrease in expense charges,
what does ICC Lomb say sir,
okay, Deepanshu, this is the recent trend and
when I refer to the mood
in the inter market, I
refer to the lower sales of April and March because the
movement of all the stock indices is due to the
loss of March only, so from the low of March,
Thousand stock has almost reached 1400
and right now it is indicating momentum as per the G,
I think the stock is in consolidation mode,
below 1320, which is a big range, where
I think
we can prefer to buy for once, but no,
Deepanshu, I think it will remain aside limited, it is
not going above 1360, 1380, only on the other
hand if 13 20 13  If 10 comes then
according to me you should review it and buy it but this
talk on more list consolidation would be n butter